Welcome to section 6 in the section.
We're going to take a quick break
from exploring new react features to
talk about a little bit of tooling
and the tool we're going to cover in
this section is webpack webpack is
an asset bundle or it's going to
combine all of the assets that make
up our application with all of the
assets needed from third-party
libraries.
And this is going to allow us to do
a couple of exciting thinks it's
going to allow us to take advantage
of third-party libraries in our
projects to remember earlier.
I talked about that vast ecosystem
of libraries that you can use the
solve common problems like date
Pickers or drag-and-drop.
We're now actually going to be able
to start to take advantage of that.
The second great thing we're going
to be able to do with webpack is
we're going to be able to take our
own application code and break it up
across multiple files.
So we want to be in a situation
where each component lives in its
own file Soar application is easier
to man.
Now the sections going to start off
with a basic introduction of webpack
along the way will be configuring it
and exploring all of the features it
provides.
All right, let's Jump Right In.